libertyunyielding.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy / Terms & Conditions - Liberty Unyielding

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which this website collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the Libertyunyielding.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Site.

If you are located in the EU, you will also be asked to provide clear and unequivocal affirmative consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your user information via cookies and similar technologies.

Notice to EU Individuals: this Privacy Statement and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR. 

**Personal Identification Information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal Identification Information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Cookies**

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit this Site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. [AdChoices](https://quantcast.com/adchoices-pub?pub=WoWE9Qi0n5mnqUmRPHkWRQ)

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s browsing history. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads based on User’s visit to this Site and/or other websites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [adssettings.google.com/authenticated](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated)

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other websites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

For EU individuals, essential cookies also help inform Site whether you require, or have already been served, an affirmative consent request in connection with the GDPR. Essential cookies include analytics cookies, which provide us data that allows Site to better understand its users and improve the Site based on what we have learned from that data.

Notwithstanding any other provision, we partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you. Our partners may place or recognize a cookie on your computer, device, or directly in our emails/communications, and we may share personal information with them if you have submitted such information to us, such as your name, postal address, or email address. Our partners may link the nonpersonal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information. Our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes. For example, our partners may deliver an ad to you in your web browser based on a purchase you made in a physical retail store, or they may send a personalized marketing email to you based on the fact that you visited a particular website.

To learn more about interest-based advertising in general and to opt out, please visit [optout.aboutads.info](http://optout.aboutads.info/) and/or [optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/) and/or [preferences-mgr.truste.com](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), or if located in the European Union please visit [youronlinechoices.eu](https://youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

**Third Party Websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

**How we use collected information**

This Site collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

  * To improve customer service; Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To personalize user experience; We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
  * To improve our Site; We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * To process transactions; We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
  * To administer a content, promotion, survey or other Site feature
  * To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
  * To send periodic emails

The email address Users provide for order processing will be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order, and information and updates about other store items. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. We do not rent, sell or barter your email address to third parties. Users may receive occasional emails from underwriters of this website; such sponsorships enable us to continue to bring you the latest news and information free of charge. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, simply click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

Site may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law such as to comply with a subpoena or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to conform to the edicts of the law, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on Site or to protect and defend the rights or property of Site.

Notice to EU Individuals: As outlined in this Privacy Statement, Site will not process your user information without a lawful basis to do so, as such bases are defined in Article 6 of the GDPR. In general, Site will process your user information on the legal bases of consent, contract (if you have entered into an agreement with us and such processing is a necessary part thereof), or legal obligation (as noted above). Site may also process certain user information on the basis of the following legitimate interests, provided that such interests are not overridden by your privacy rights and interests: delivering and continuing to develop and improve the Site, learning from your behavior on the Site (e.g., analyzing traffic) to better serve you and other Site users, helping us modify or enhance the Site and its content, receiving insight as to what users do (and don’t) like about our Site or aspects thereof, and providing a stable, consistent, and secure user experience in connection with the Site.

**How We Protect Your Information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Cross-border Transfers**

Your user information may be transferred to other countries in connection with your use of the Site. If you access or use the Site outside of the United States, your user information will be transferred to our servers in the United States.

Site participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Site is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, respectively, in reliance on each Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at https://www.privacyshield.gov/list. Site is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under each Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Site complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Site is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Site may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Copyright**

All content on this Site is copyrighted. Reposting and reuse are permissible only with the expressed permission. [Copyright.gov](https://www.copyright.gov/fair-use/more-info.html) offers guidelines regarding what actions exceed the scope of “fair use.”

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

This Site has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please feel free to [contact us](https://libertyunyielding.com/contact/).
